# Ibtehal Y. Alwazir

Energetic, adaptable, and self-motivated with solid qualifications in an array of Project Management experiences with ability to work effectively both individually and part of a team. Passion for learning and growing to become part of an innovative company, offering both creative and analytical opportunities.

Desapandan 55100 Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia +60104349930 ibtehalyahia123@gmail.com

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## Stratford International Language Center, KL, Malaysia— Marketing and Sales Officer

May 2016 - August 2021

Strategically oversaw a diverse range of responsibilities by being an integrated partner supporting the Center's growth and day to day functions that support goals to enhance revenue.

Prepared ongoing analysis and suitable marketing material

Established new and existing student relationships with the Center

### Alreda Medical Center, Sana'a, Yemen — Office Manager

September 2012 - June 2015

Coordinated day-to-day office operations and ensured delivery of high-quality care for patients.

Maintained medical records system archive

Managed and monitored medical and office supplies budget

Supervised administrative staff implementing office policies processing payments, maintaining cleanliness and security of facility

Reviewed monthly financial reports

# Social Fund for Development (SFD), Sana'a, Yemen—Administrative Assistant

November 2010 - January 2012 (started as an intern and confirmed full-time employee as of July 2011)

Prepared annual work plans for SFD with indicators considering geographical and sectoral fund allocation

Screened projects, appraised and selected according to SFD eligibility criteria

Monitored and implemented projects in accordance with operations manual

Created and published newsletter that included the monthly progress report

Coordinated corporate events (overseas conferences) including booking and managing flights, confirming route, lodging and dates

Managed Meeting Minutes and Memos of corporate meetings

Learned knowledge of maintaining fund accounts, reviewing international funding contracts and implementing projects according to contract

#### **CITIZENSHIP & LANGUAGES**

Yemen and British Passport Holder

Fluent in English and Arabic (Speaking, Reading and Writing)

## Kids Planet School, Sana'a, Yemen — Kindergarten Teacher

August 2008 - June 2010

Design and prepare lessons for reading, mathematics and social education programs

Compile and organize learning materials and props and apply various instructional methods.

Teach numeracy and alphabet and present storytelling, songs and structured games, art and music while engaging the child in emotional and social interpersonal skills

Maintain lines of communication with parents and provide regular monthly feedback through assessment reports

#### **EDUCATION**

## London Metropolitan University — Dubai, UAE

August 2003 - June 2007

• Bachelor's Degree in Computer Studies and Information System

## Yemen American Language Center (YALI) — Sana'a, Yemen

August 2009 - June 2012

• A completion of Advanced English Language course